const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'אֶבֶן',
    answers: ['steen'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'דּוֹר',
    answers: ['geslacht', 'generatie'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'יְרוּשָׁלַיִם',
    answers: ['Jeruzalem'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'כֹּה',
    answers: ['zo', 'aldus'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'לֶחֶם',
    answers: ['brood', 'strijd'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'מִדְבָּר',
    answers: ['woestijn', 'wildernis', 'mond'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'מָה',
    answers: ['wat', 'wat voor een', 'hoe', 'waarom'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'מִי',
    answers: ['wie', 'iemand'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'מִשְׁפָּט',
    answers: ['rechtspraak', 'uitspraak', 'vonnis', 'recht', 'gerechtigheid'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'משֶׁה',
    answers: ['Mozes'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'נָבִיא',
    answers: ['profeet'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'נַעַר',
    answers: ['jongen', 'knecht'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'נַעֲרָה',
    answers: ['meisje', 'dienstmaagd'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'סֵפֶר',
    answers: ['geschrift', 'brief', 'document', 'boek', 'register'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'פֶּן',
    answers: ['opdat niet', 'want anders'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'רֶגֶל',
    answers: ['voet', 'been'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שֶׁמֶן',
    answers: ['vet', 'olie'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'תּוֹרָה',
    answers: ['onderwijzing', 'wet'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'הוּא',
    answers: ['hij', 'die', 'dat'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'הִיא',
    answers: ['zij', 'die', 'dat'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אַתָּה',
    answers: ['jij'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אַתְּ',
    answers: ['jij'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אֲנִי',
    answers: ['ik'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אָנֹכִי',
    answers: ['ik'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'הֵם',
    answers: ['zij', 'die'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'הֵמָּה',
    answers: ['zij', 'die'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'הֵנָּה',
    answers: ['zij', 'die'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אַתֶּם',
    answers: ['jullie'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אַתֵּן',
    answers: ['jullie'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אַתֵּנָה',
    answers: ['jullie'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'נַחְנוּ',
    answers: ['wij'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אֲנַחְנוּ',
    answers: ['wij'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'זֶה',
    answers: ['deze', 'dit'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'זֹאת',
    answers: ['deze', 'dit'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אֵלֶּה',
    answers: ['deze'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson8Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson8-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 8 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson8Vocabulary
